PPO FULL12 | checkpoint 171520 | SAFETY_ABORT
FL  front left
FR  front right
RL  rear left
RR  rear right
NATIVE joint-axis signs. canonical -> native: FL -1, FR +1, RL -1, RR +1.
Measured ankle angular qd [rad/s], NOT wheel-center translation. No encoded tick0; first frame is tick8.
1x / 15fps | tick 8 | sim 0.067s | P01 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.0745
actual  -0.2031
target  -0.0281
actual  -0.0278
target  +0.0302
actual  +0.0306
target  +0.0805
actual  +0.0101
1x / 15fps | tick 16 | sim 0.133s | P01 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1322
actual  -0.0008
target  -0.0510
actual  -0.0497
target  +0.0582
actual  +0.0584
target  +0.1478
actual  +0.0294
1x / 15fps | tick 24 | sim 0.200s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1788
actual  +0.0272
target  -0.0705
actual  -0.0682
target  +0.0814
actual  +0.0815
target  +0.2027
actual  +0.0786
1x / 15fps | tick 32 | sim 0.267s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.2176
actual  +0.0215
target  -0.0877
actual  -0.0850
target  +0.1021
actual  +0.1026
target  +0.2494
actual  +0.0556
1x / 15fps | tick 40 | sim 0.333s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.2522
actual  +0.0102
target  -0.1044
actual  -0.1026
target  +0.1218
actual  +0.1233
target  +0.2907
actual  +0.2037
1x / 15fps | tick 48 | sim 0.400s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  -0.0183
actual  -0.2445
target  +0.1804
actual  +0.1829
target  -0.1603
actual  -0.1609
target  +0.6256
actual  +0.5157
1x / 15fps | tick 56 | sim 0.467s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.0058
actual  -0.1645
target  +0.1662
actual  +0.1670
target  -0.1436
actual  -0.1426
target  +0.6548
actual  +0.6169
1x / 15fps | tick 64 | sim 0.533s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.0253
actual  -0.1553
target  +0.1538
actual  +0.1546
target  -0.1290
actual  -0.1283
target  +0.6787
actual  +0.6561
1x / 15fps | tick 72 | sim 0.600s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.0415
actual  -0.1305
target  +0.1424
actual  +0.1439
target  -0.1161
actual  -0.1155
target  +0.6984
actual  +1.1340
1x / 15fps | tick 80 | sim 0.667s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.0542
actual  +0.1713
target  +0.1321
actual  +0.1345
target  -0.1047
actual  -0.2887
target  +0.7143
actual  +0.7599
1x / 15fps | tick 88 | sim 0.733s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.0686
actual  +0.4852
target  +0.1209
actual  +0.1249
target  -0.0942
actual  -0.1091
target  +0.7286
actual  +0.7320
1x / 15fps | tick 96 | sim 0.800s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.0849
actual  +0.2328
target  +0.1092
actual  +0.1087
target  -0.0832
actual  -0.0964
target  +0.7421
actual  +0.5730
1x / 15fps | tick 104 | sim 0.867s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.0987
actual  +0.2420
target  +0.0994
actual  +0.1027
target  -0.0743
actual  -0.0789
target  +0.7530
actual  +0.6864
1x / 15fps | tick 112 | sim 0.933s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1096
actual  -0.0150
target  +0.0903
actual  +0.0920
target  -0.0661
actual  -0.0405
target  +0.7612
actual  +0.6421
1x / 15fps | tick 120 | sim 1.000s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1206
actual  -0.1534
target  +0.0820
actual  +0.0844
target  -0.0585
actual  -0.0363
target  +0.7690
actual  +0.6174
1x / 15fps | tick 128 | sim 1.067s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1297
actual  -0.1702
target  +0.0748
actual  +0.0755
target  -0.0519
actual  +0.0204
target  +0.7753
actual  +0.6905
1x / 15fps | tick 136 | sim 1.133s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1387
actual  -0.0637
target  +0.0679
actual  +0.0664
target  -0.0454
actual  +0.0241
target  +0.7813
actual  +0.7620
1x / 15fps | tick 144 | sim 1.200s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1458
actual  -0.0401
target  +0.0623
actual  +0.0637
target  -0.0405
actual  -0.1432
target  +0.7861
actual  +0.6993
1x / 15fps | tick 152 | sim 1.267s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1499
actual  -0.0282
target  +0.0582
actual  +0.0600
target  -0.0365
actual  -0.0016
target  +0.7893
actual  +0.7188
1x / 15fps | tick 160 | sim 1.333s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1537
actual  -0.0499
target  +0.0544
actual  +0.0550
target  -0.0332
actual  +0.0751
target  +0.7920
actual  +0.7187
1x / 15fps | tick 168 | sim 1.400s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1573
actual  -0.0630
target  +0.0510
actual  +0.0526
target  -0.0304
actual  +0.1019
target  +0.7945
actual  +0.7251
1x / 15fps | tick 176 | sim 1.467s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1605
actual  -0.0026
target  +0.0478
actual  +0.0497
target  -0.0274
actual  -0.0113
target  +0.7966
actual  +0.6891
1x / 15fps | tick 184 | sim 1.533s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1631
actual  +0.0171
target  +0.0451
actual  +0.0447
target  -0.0251
actual  +0.0271
target  +0.7983
actual  +0.6998
1x / 15fps | tick 192 | sim 1.600s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1653
actual  -0.0320
target  +0.0430
actual  +0.0432
target  -0.0234
actual  +0.0500
target  +0.7997
actual  +0.6957
1x / 15fps | tick 200 | sim 1.667s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1675
actual  -0.0105
target  +0.0408
actual  +0.0432
target  -0.0216
actual  -0.0009
target  +0.8010
actual  +0.7766
1x / 15fps | tick 208 | sim 1.733s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1691
actual  -0.0506
target  +0.0390
actual  +0.0391
target  -0.0199
actual  +0.0559
target  +0.8019
actual  +0.7429
1x / 15fps | tick 216 | sim 1.800s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1709
actual  +0.0069
target  +0.0371
actual  +0.0377
target  -0.0181
actual  +0.0462
target  +0.8028
actual  +0.7399
1x / 15fps | tick 224 | sim 1.867s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1727
actual  -0.0002
target  +0.0353
actual  +0.0357
target  -0.0164
actual  +0.0400
target  +0.8037
actual  +0.7478
1x / 15fps | tick 232 | sim 1.933s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1740
actual  -0.0659
target  +0.0338
actual  +0.0345
target  -0.0149
actual  -0.0244
target  +0.8042
actual  +0.8610
1x / 15fps | tick 240 | sim 2.000s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1752
actual  +0.0297
target  +0.0327
actual  +0.0329
target  -0.0139
actual  -0.0234
target  +0.8048
actual  +0.7224
1x / 15fps | tick 248 | sim 2.067s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1768
actual  +0.0058
target  +0.0317
actual  +0.0307
target  -0.0130
actual  +0.0131
target  +0.8055
actual  +0.7321
1x / 15fps | tick 256 | sim 2.133s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1780
actual  -0.0810
target  +0.0309
actual  +0.0297
target  -0.0123
actual  -0.0228
target  +0.8060
actual  +0.7086
1x / 15fps | tick 264 | sim 2.200s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1792
actual  -0.0260
target  +0.0303
actual  +0.0318
target  -0.0116
actual  -0.0205
target  +0.8065
actual  +0.7404
1x / 15fps | tick 272 | sim 2.267s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1803
actual  -0.0743
target  +0.0296
actual  +0.0287
target  -0.0109
actual  +0.0248
target  +0.8070
actual  +0.7309
1x / 15fps | tick 280 | sim 2.333s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1814
actual  +0.0215
target  +0.0289
actual  +0.0289
target  -0.0099
actual  +0.0329
target  +0.8075
actual  +0.7410
1x / 15fps | tick 288 | sim 2.400s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1824
actual  -0.0223
target  +0.0281
actual  +0.0285
target  -0.0092
actual  +0.0006
target  +0.8079
actual  +0.7217
1x / 15fps | tick 296 | sim 2.467s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1834
actual  +0.0038
target  +0.0276
actual  +0.0266
target  -0.0087
actual  +0.0101
target  +0.8083
actual  +0.7019
1x / 15fps | tick 304 | sim 2.533s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1841
actual  +0.0467
target  +0.0273
actual  +0.0270
target  -0.0084
actual  -0.0091
target  +0.8086
actual  +0.6825
1x / 15fps | tick 312 | sim 2.600s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1850
actual  +0.0607
target  +0.0269
actual  +0.0277
target  -0.0081
actual  +0.0033
target  +0.8090
actual  +0.6876
1x / 15fps | tick 320 | sim 2.667s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1855
actual  +0.0119
target  +0.0266
actual  +0.0258
target  -0.0078
actual  +0.0360
target  +0.8092
actual  +0.7020
1x / 15fps | tick 328 | sim 2.733s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1861
actual  -0.0207
target  +0.0263
actual  +0.0267
target  -0.0075
actual  +0.0016
target  +0.8094
actual  +0.6738
1x / 15fps | tick 336 | sim 2.800s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1866
actual  +0.0554
target  +0.0260
actual  +0.0262
target  -0.0073
actual  +0.0198
target  +0.8095
actual  +0.5795
1x / 15fps | tick 344 | sim 2.867s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1871
actual  +0.0430
target  +0.0257
actual  +0.0248
target  -0.0071
actual  +0.0085
target  +0.8097
actual  +0.7235
1x / 15fps | tick 352 | sim 2.933s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1875
actual  +0.0543
target  +0.0256
actual  +0.0258
target  -0.0070
actual  +0.0161
target  +0.8099
actual  +0.7062
1x / 15fps | tick 360 | sim 3.000s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1878
actual  +0.0498
target  +0.0254
actual  +0.0256
target  -0.0069
actual  +0.0184
target  +0.8100
actual  +0.7377
1x / 15fps | tick 368 | sim 3.067s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1881
actual  +0.0617
target  +0.0253
actual  +0.0254
target  -0.0068
actual  +0.0119
target  +0.8101
actual  +0.7157
1x / 15fps | tick 376 | sim 3.133s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1884
actual  -0.0086
target  +0.0251
actual  +0.0252
target  -0.0067
actual  +0.0090
target  +0.8102
actual  +0.7215
1x / 15fps | tick 384 | sim 3.200s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1884
actual  +0.0736
target  +0.0251
actual  +0.0261
target  -0.0067
actual  -0.0083
target  +0.8101
actual  +0.6789
1x / 15fps | tick 392 | sim 3.267s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1886
actual  +0.0722
target  +0.0250
actual  +0.0264
target  -0.0066
actual  -0.0048
target  +0.8102
actual  +0.8982
1x / 15fps | tick 400 | sim 3.333s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1890
actual  +0.0564
target  +0.0248
actual  +0.0249
target  -0.0064
actual  +0.0169
target  +0.8104
actual  +0.6842
1x / 15fps | tick 408 | sim 3.400s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1892
actual  +0.0706
target  +0.0247
actual  +0.0256
target  -0.0065
actual  -0.0074
target  +0.8104
actual  +0.6696
1x / 15fps | tick 416 | sim 3.467s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1893
actual  +0.0667
target  +0.0246
actual  +0.0244
target  -0.0064
actual  +0.0253
target  +0.8105
actual  +0.7314
1x / 15fps | tick 424 | sim 3.533s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1894
actual  +0.0062
target  +0.0247
actual  +0.0251
target  -0.0065
actual  -0.0027
target  +0.8105
actual  +0.6896
1x / 15fps | tick 432 | sim 3.600s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1894
actual  +0.0633
target  +0.0246
actual  +0.0252
target  -0.0065
actual  -0.0149
target  +0.8105
actual  +0.6809
1x / 15fps | tick 440 | sim 3.667s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1896
actual  -0.0200
target  +0.0245
actual  +0.0246
target  -0.0065
actual  -0.0148
target  +0.8105
actual  +0.6968
1x / 15fps | tick 448 | sim 3.733s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1895
actual  +0.0957
target  +0.0246
actual  +0.0256
target  -0.0066
actual  -0.0153
target  +0.8104
actual  +0.6860
1x / 15fps | tick 456 | sim 3.800s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1896
actual  +0.0511
target  +0.0246
actual  +0.0243
target  -0.0066
actual  +0.0230
target  +0.8105
actual  +0.6808
1x / 15fps | tick 464 | sim 3.867s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1897
actual  +0.0587
target  +0.0245
actual  +0.0240
target  -0.0066
actual  -0.0098
target  +0.8105
actual  +0.7361
1x / 15fps | tick 472 | sim 3.933s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1897
actual  +0.0766
target  +0.0246
actual  +0.0253
target  -0.0068
actual  -0.0174
target  +0.8105
actual  +0.6895
1x / 15fps | tick 480 | sim 4.000s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1898
actual  +0.0582
target  +0.0245
actual  +0.0249
target  -0.0066
actual  -0.0198
target  +0.8105
actual  +0.7158
1x / 15fps | tick 488 | sim 4.067s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1897
actual  +0.0741
target  +0.0245
actual  +0.0264
target  -0.0067
actual  -0.0232
target  +0.8105
actual  +0.7735
1x / 15fps | tick 496 | sim 4.133s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1899
actual  +0.0684
target  +0.0245
actual  +0.0255
target  -0.0067
actual  -0.0200
target  +0.8106
actual  +0.6915
1x / 15fps | tick 504 | sim 4.200s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1901
actual  +0.0585
target  +0.0244
actual  +0.0248
target  -0.0066
actual  -0.0263
target  +0.8107
actual  +0.6908
1x / 15fps | tick 512 | sim 4.267s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1900
actual  +0.0601
target  +0.0244
actual  +0.0248
target  -0.0067
actual  -0.0300
target  +0.8107
actual  +0.6947
1x / 15fps | tick 520 | sim 4.333s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1899
actual  +0.0924
target  +0.0244
actual  +0.0252
target  -0.0068
actual  -0.0264
target  +0.8106
actual  +0.7400
1x / 15fps | tick 528 | sim 4.400s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1903
actual  +0.0591
target  +0.0242
actual  +0.0246
target  -0.0066
actual  -0.0340
target  +0.8108
actual  +0.6817
1x / 15fps | tick 536 | sim 4.467s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1901
actual  +0.0575
target  +0.0242
actual  +0.0246
target  -0.0067
actual  -0.0371
target  +0.8107
actual  +0.6517
1x / 15fps | tick 544 | sim 4.533s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1901
actual  +0.0839
target  +0.0243
actual  +0.0251
target  -0.0068
actual  -0.0310
target  +0.8107
actual  +0.6497
1x / 15fps | tick 552 | sim 4.600s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1900
actual  +0.0549
target  +0.0243
actual  +0.0247
target  -0.0069
actual  -0.0419
target  +0.8106
actual  +0.6570
1x / 15fps | tick 560 | sim 4.667s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1899
actual  +0.0762
target  +0.0244
actual  +0.0246
target  -0.0070
actual  -0.0416
target  +0.8106
actual  +0.6432
1x / 15fps | tick 568 | sim 4.733s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1898
actual  +0.0624
target  +0.0244
actual  +0.0245
target  -0.0071
actual  -0.0563
target  +0.8105
actual  +0.6343
1x / 15fps | tick 576 | sim 4.800s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1899
actual  +0.0591
target  +0.0243
actual  +0.0254
target  -0.0071
actual  -0.0553
target  +0.8106
actual  +0.9427
1x / 15fps | tick 584 | sim 4.867s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1900
actual  -0.0249
target  +0.0242
actual  +0.0239
target  -0.0071
actual  -0.0658
target  +0.8107
actual  +0.6280
1x / 15fps | tick 592 | sim 4.933s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1904
actual  -0.0049
target  +0.0240
actual  +0.0231
target  -0.0070
actual  -0.0745
target  +0.8108
actual  +0.6346
1x / 15fps | tick 600 | sim 5.000s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1908
actual  +0.1064
target  +0.0237
actual  +0.0242
target  -0.0066
actual  -0.0412
target  +0.8111
actual  +0.6101
1x / 15fps | tick 608 | sim 5.067s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1913
actual  +0.0907
target  +0.0234
actual  +0.0238
target  -0.0063
actual  -0.0414
target  +0.8113
actual  +0.6142
1x / 15fps | tick 616 | sim 5.133s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1921
actual  +0.0604
target  +0.0229
actual  +0.0237
target  -0.0058
actual  -0.0629
target  +0.8116
actual  +0.6274
1x / 15fps | tick 624 | sim 5.200s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1927
actual  +0.0794
target  +0.0225
actual  +0.0211
target  -0.0052
actual  -0.0581
target  +0.8118
actual  +0.6644
1x / 15fps | tick 632 | sim 5.267s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1925
actual  +0.0937
target  +0.0228
actual  +0.0232
target  -0.0057
actual  -0.0239
target  +0.8118
actual  +0.5991
1x / 15fps | tick 640 | sim 5.333s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1923
actual  +0.0566
target  +0.0230
actual  +0.0231
target  -0.0060
actual  -0.0289
target  +0.8117
actual  +0.6220
1x / 15fps | tick 648 | sim 5.400s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1921
actual  +0.0565
target  +0.0232
actual  +0.0234
target  -0.0063
actual  -0.0318
target  +0.8116
actual  +0.5876
1x / 15fps | tick 656 | sim 5.467s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1918
actual  -0.0372
target  +0.0234
actual  +0.0232
target  -0.0066
actual  -0.0375
target  +0.8115
actual  +0.6523
1x / 15fps | tick 664 | sim 5.533s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1916
actual  +0.0402
target  +0.0236
actual  +0.0231
target  -0.0070
actual  -0.0558
target  +0.8113
actual  +0.5675
1x / 15fps | tick 672 | sim 5.600s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1913
actual  +0.0622
target  +0.0238
actual  +0.0244
target  -0.0072
actual  -0.0074
target  +0.8111
actual  +0.5403
1x / 15fps | tick 680 | sim 5.667s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1910
actual  +0.0150
target  +0.0240
actual  +0.0232
target  -0.0075
actual  -0.0509
target  +0.8109
actual  +0.6671
1x / 15fps | tick 688 | sim 5.733s | P02 | LIVE actual frame
target  +0.1908
actual  +0.0588
target  +0.0242
actual  +0.0228
target  -0.0078
actual  -0.0611
target  +0.8108
actual  +0.4751
1x / 15fps | tick 693 | sim 5.775s | P02 | RUN ENDED - SAFETY_ABORT
target  +0.1909
actual  +0.0063
target  +0.0242
actual  +0.0234
target  -0.0080
actual  -0.0429
target  +0.8108
actual  +0.4409